hi guys welcome
back this channel is all about exploring
new things and bits and pieces about
me this is nothing but a product review
video a brand called
happs people comment fake video
sponsor and all that before you comment
all that
just go
doch there's not you know that much of
views and
all really
think brand where their products cost in
thousands they will give to me in free
or they will give me some money to talk
about
their you
know some people
say
yes I do have the point
is
first of all it's all natural organic
and
components once
you
re for me to for
[Music]
it I don't use it every single
day
so choose the right product and apply to
your skin opinion I'm not you
know just a common person just like you
also tell before the bottles are
empti because the color
it's
getting so first turmeric night cream
Maya Anda brightening cream SOA is
basically it's a
moisturizer it's just very simple like
yes okay this is the quantity I take
very little very little so this is how
you apply theala cream
[Music]
so
it's like
very
okay so this is the way you
[Music]
apply
because less is
more not supposed to take a lot and do
that same goes with the termeric night
cream so this is the way you use this so
this is about this and
soap
andap just wanted to get it because it
smells so
good experience oh my
godell so
fantastic I don't know how to express
Only If you experience you know
that same goes with this
with those creams
and
faceh rir so
Rosa
but I just love this and the smell and
everything when I put my
make so
faceh so always a go
to it's
not to
mon that's about this
and this and little tint of foundation
so tone of skin lighter brighter
like little
bit so that's something really good
about
thiser this and thise and ginger flavor
and it's a very vety
flavor
[Music]
so that's something
I coming to the latest purchase
thiron
not a person to do it
every so that's that's my morning what I
do
I'm just loving this
product the strawberry yeah strawberry
tinted lips so sample it's very small
when you go when you buy
on Curry leaf and the goberry wheat
protein so first with the goberry
Keratin wheat protein
which in one one part it is
good I go with this the go shampoo and
for the
conditioner
this it's
amaz
and then I wanted to try
this the point is if my hair is not
treated it is treated since this is all
organic and natural and otic and all I
feel up to the
support
I got
this
Wasim so yeah guys
Happ prodct Rev
please do check out my other two videos
on Happy OBS product review one and two
almost we've come to the end of the
video a big thank you that really means
a lot to me subscribe a bigger thank you
please do consider subscribing that
really mean so much to me
and catch an interesting video t
byebye